CAITLIN WHITELEY

INGLESIDE, LANSDOWN ROAD, BATH, BA1 5SU

M: 07769 173361 | H: 01225 480936 | caitlin.whiteley@hotmail.co.uk | DOB: 19/09/1996

PROFILE

I am a friendly, conscientious, and hard-working graduate with over a year's worth of customer services experience, and programming skills in both Python and VBA (Excel). I spent last summer working in the operations office at a food factory, where I gained experience in a busy and varied environment. Working in retail has taught me the importance of good and effective customer relations, and alongside education and extracurricular sports, has given me valuable time management skills.

EDUCATION

DURHAM UNIVERSITY | 2015-2018

BSc Maths, 2:2

During my first year, I studied joint honours Maths and Physics, transferring onto straight Maths at the beginning of my second year. This enabled me to choose more interesting and specialised modules, rather than being restricted to the core modules of both subjects. In my third year, I focused on Applied Maths, as I enjoy the relevance to real situations, and gained a high first in my final year dissertation.

HAYESFIELD GIRLS' SCHOOL | 2007-2015

A levels: A*AAB in Maths, Further Maths, Physics and Chemistry

GCSEs: 8A*s and 4As. At GSCE, I was awarded the April Payne prize for Mathematics for hard work and dedication to the subject, and the Oldfield Prize for Excellence in my overall GCSE results.

WORK EXPERIENCE

EDWARD BILLINGTON & SONS LTD

Summer Internship | July - September 2017

I worked in a dynamic food factory (Bar Foods), that manufactures ready meals and sauces for high street restaurants. I mainly worked in the operations office, where I learnt to use Excel VBA. A significant part of the job was writing code for the planning process, working to make the complex weekly production plan quicker and more efficient, as well as editing old code to significantly reduce programme running times. I also worked in the finance department, helping sort invoices, and improving their spreadsheets with shortcuts to enable smoother and easier customer order control.

SERVE LEGAL

Secret shopper | October 2013 - September 2016

With Serve Legal, I ensured that retail outlets were complying with sales legislation for young consumers regarding alcohol, tobacco and betting. I also gave the retailers feedback on the customer service I received, which has helped me understand the importance of implementing effective compliance and management control systems.

WAITROSE

Customer Services | October 2013 - March 2015

During my A-Levels, I had a part-time job working directly with the customers, where I learned the importance of customer service and time management, as well as having to think and act quickly when problems arose. This primarily involved working on the tills, and I also worked in the café and some shifts on queue control over the Christmas period.

Other work experience includes waitressing with a Silver Service catering company, and bar work at Bath Rugby Club.

EXTRA CURRICULAR

- Throughout my three years at University, I represented Durham University in national competitions for cheerleading, gymnastics, and trampolining. My greatest success was winning first place at the University National Championships with our level 5 cheerleading stunt group.
- I had executive roles for the cheerleading squad, including vice-captain, treasurer and uniform officer. I also ran the strength and conditioning training programme for the gymnastic and trampolining teams.
- I started gymnastics as a toddler, and kept it up until University, and throughout my time there. Since graduating, I have joined a level 5 cheerleading squad in Bristol, where we compete nationally and are aiming to win a place to compete at the World Championships in April.
- I also have my Silver Duke of Edinburgh award, and RYA Level 3 sailing certificate.

REFERENCES

Covering both academic and employment, references are available upon request.